Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Wildlife photography!
Taking walks and playing games when they're sunny
Bucky!
Who put the trees like this?
All random and messy?
You can't even get through them!
This forest needs work!
Bucky!
Hey!
Oh!
Take that tree!
Yeah!
I am the lumberjack architect undisputed master of the forest!
And I say to burn!
Look out!
Huh?
What?
Whoa!
Bjorn!
Hey!
Hello!
What's going on, buddy?
Hey Bucky, I'm just trying to observe the beauty of nature
Or I was just doing that
Let me see!
Where's the nature?
Where's the beauty?
Come on!
There!
I just don't see any nature!
Well, Bucky, the nature ran away!
Because someone scared it off!
Huh?
Nature should be observed silently!
And from a nice distance!
Oh, right!
Tell that to the forest!
Cause it pops and crunches with every single step I take!
Huh!
I do tend to stomp around a lot, I guess!
Oh, hey!
I'll find a way to observe nature's beauty from a nice distance!
It'll work even if I'm noisy!
And I'm always noisy!
Hmm, not this!
This stuff!
And all this stuff, too!
Tripod!
Oh!
Alright!
Good!
With equipment like this, I can observe the stuffing out of nature!
Yeah!
Now I just need to find some nature to try it out on!
Bingo!
Just act natural!
Come on!
I just want to observe your beauty!
Where'd you go?
There you are!
Nature!
Here, chicky, chicky, chicky!
Chicky!
The nature just disappeared! What do I do now?
Think, Bucky!
It's no problem!
Bjorn's gonna love this thing!
Because it's awesome!
Scientists and others with big, smart brains will tell you that nature has sort of a problem with loud noises.
Okay...
So, what then are all those...
Long pause for dramatic effect...
Who are by their very nature loudmouths...
Ever to do!
Well now, Bucky's latest invention has solved this terrible problem!
I give you the remarkable nature-looky thing!
Speechless, huh? Check it out!
You spot some sweet nature, right? But it's a very long distance off!
Feel free to take notes!
Well, in that case, you just press the zoom button!
Zoom!
Nature crab!
Then, just observe the grand beauty of nature!
When you've seen enough, back it goes!
Where do you think you're going?
Bad nature!
Fine!
How about now?
So, nature's far better when...
My super technology enhances it, right?
Well, Bucky, technology's nice.
But, up north, we take kind of a different approach when we're observing nature.
Why don't you just come with me and see?
That's so cool!
Hello, Owl!
Shhh!
Sorry!
Hello, Owl!
They're so beautiful!
Blue Moose!
I wondered what that frog was so afraid of!
I can't wait till they hatch!
Uh, no comment.
These are awesome!
This is how nature should be observed!
That's right!
When nature can't tell you're there, you can see much more of what nature does!
It's cool to meet you, nature!
You are awesome!
I'm Sharp!
I'm and your Ramona.
I'm David Vulture.
I'm Fields Pat
Sousowed on our dialogs at Bahrain,
We're some of those times.
The only way through on ournguixos16.
Beautiful!
Your Stamets to have a great job in the empire.
That's awesome!
That's impressive!
We're here to Halfway Shell!
You can still be here in an annual a택rol.
Remember to be here?
You can still like ur community,
Where you can continue to Nahมuixos3.