Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
La la la la!
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
La la la la!
When you spend it with a friend
Just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
The House Spirit
This is a million percent true
It was a dark and stormy night
I was in my house all by myself
Working on a gadget
Which I never got to work right
But forget that
There I was, geniusing away
And then...
Then what?
I took one bite and put the cake back
It was mad tasty by the way
Right, but then when I looked...
Cake?
Where are you?
Gone?
Completely gone!
The whole piece!
I'd only had one bite!
And then what?
Well, that was how it started
Ever since, whenever I looked the other way
Blam!
My food vanishes!
This one time, I was reading this really hard book for super smart bears
And...
Can you believe it?
Blam!
Completely empty?
And it's happened other times too
Huh?
When I'm meditating...
Oh!
Or working out...
Whoa!
I mean...
At its core?
There's something really fishy going on...
It started happening all the time!
Huh?
Oh!
It's even sort of scary!
If all my food just keeps disappearing...
What am I supposed to do?
Think maybe...
I could just stay with you...
Until this problem stops?
Listen Bucky...
We have this ancient legend up north where I come from...
They say that in the den of every bear...
There lives a house spirit...
Whoa!
And if the bear does something to upset him...
He will become angry...
And then he'll start playing all sorts of mean bad tricks!
Huh?
Just be quiet with your made up ghost stories!
Modern science guides this bear's life!
Look!
Excuse me!
I'm back!
I'm talking formulas, theorems, and proofs!
Elegant math equations!
Backed up by advanced, complex, state-of-the-art lab experiments!
Really sciency-science!
Through which I've absolutely proven beyond a shadow of a doubt...
That dumb house spirits just do not exist!
But your food keeps disappearing, doesn't it?
Hmm...
All right, fine!
If I have a house spirit, why'd he become a food thief?
He never took anything before!
I'm not sure!
I guess that he's upset!
Upset?
At what?
Just look at the sweet place he gets to call home!
Spacious, warm, stylish, bright...
Brilliant feng shui!
You know, Bucky...
While it's true you have a wonderfully nice place to live in here...
But it's...
A bit of a terrible mess!
I'd be upset if I had to live here!
If you had looked where you were stepping, you'd have no reason to be upset!
And this is not just some ordinary mess!
It's a creative genius mess!
It's like the inside of my brain!
Whoa!
My brain's a mess!
Perhaps we should tidy up anyway!
I can help, you know!
Here we go!
Careful, buddy!
We're getting pretty good at this!
Well, if it isn't Mr. Buttons!
Whoa!
I lost that!
Like four whole months ago!
What is this thing?
So, I thought I should be prepared in case aliens ever land here!
Of course I would need to document the moment!
So I set up surveillance cameras all over the house!
So, did the aliens ever actually come?
Not yet!
Could be they took a wrong turn!
Alien GPS is buggy!
Are the cameras still all recording stuff?
Of course!
Bjorn, you're a genius!
Now, thanks to modern technology and my amazing brain's first-rate thinking,
we've got footage of my house spirit!
You can totally tell I'm geniusing up a storm there!
There!
Chicky!
That naughty pumpkin!
But what's up?
Where's the house spirit?
Forward!
Chicky again!
Just wait until I get my hands on that little yellow yum burglar!
That was my honey!
Come on!
Forward!
Chicky again!
Are you kidding me?
That sneaky little beak face!
Well there!
It was just Chicky the whole time!
And you are talking about house spirits!
But your house is a lot tidier and cleaner than it used to be, Bucky!
If a house spirit was living here, he'd definitely be happier now!
That's fine by me!
I like it like this!
There's room to skateboard inside!
Ooh!
I always hide a cookie in the couch!
Where'd it go?
It had cream in the middle!
I need it!
I really need it!
Huh?
Get me back my cookie!
Hey!
Come back!
Wildlife photography!
Ah!
Woow!
Ow!
It's a straight place?!
Huh!
Hey!
I need it!
I really need it!
Huh!
Get me back my cookie!
Hey!
Come back!
Huh.
Gah-hum-hum-hum.
Hmm.
Jakin' walks and playin' games when they're sunny.
Bucky!
Who put the trees like this? All random and messy?
You can't even get through them. This forest needs work.
Bucky! Hey!
Take that, tree! Yeah!
I am the lumberjack, architect, undisputed master of the forest!
And I say to burn!
Look out!
Huh? What?
Whoa, Bjorn! Hey, hello! What's going on, buddy?
Hey, Bucky, I'm just trying to observe the beauty of nature.
Oh, or I was just doing that.
Let me see. Where's the nature? Where's the beauty? Come on!
Uh, there. I just don't see any nature.
Well, Bucky, the nature ran away.
Because someone scared it off.
Huh?
Nature should be observed silently.
And from a nice distance.
Oh, right.
Tell that to the forest.
Cause it pops and crunches with every single step I take.
I do tend to stomp around a lot, I guess.
Oh, hey!
I'll find a way to observe nature's beauty from a nice distance.
It'll work even if I'm noisy.
And I'm always noisy!
Hmm, not this.
This stuff.
And all this stuff, too.
Tripod.
Good.
With equipment like this, I can observe the stuffing out of nature.
Yay.
Now I just need to find some nature to try it out on.
Bingo!
Chicky!
Just act natural and let me observe you, alright?
Just act natural!
Come on!
I just want to observe your beauty!
Where'd you go?
There you are!
Nature!
Here, chicky, chicky, chicky!
Chicky!
The nature just disappeared.
What do I do now?
Think, Bucky!
Huh!
It's no problem!
Bjorn's gonna love this thing!
Because it's awesome!
Scientists and others with big smart brains will tell you that nature has sort of a problem with loud noises.
Okay.
So what then are all those, long pause for dramatic effect, who are by their very nature loud mouths ever to do?
Well now, Bucky's latest invention has solved this terrible problem.
I give you the remarkable nature looky thing!
Speechless, huh?
Check it out!
You spot some sweet nature, right?
But it's a very long distance off!
Feel free to take notes.
Well in that case, you just press the zoom button.
Zoom! Nature crab!
Then just observe the grand beauty of nature!
When you've seen enough, back it goes!
Where do you think you're going?
Bad nature!
Fine. How about now?
So nature's far better when my super technology enhances it, right?
Well Bucky, technology's nice, but up north we take kind of a different approach when we're observing nature.
Why don't you just come with me and see?
That's so cool!
Hello Owl!
Shhh!
Sorry!
Hello Owl!
They're so beautiful!
Blue Moose!
I wondered what that frog was so afraid of!
I can't wait till they hatch!
Uh, no comment.
Ha ha!
These are awesome!
This is how nature should be observed!
That's right!
When nature can't tell you're there, you can see much more of what nature does!
It's cool to meet you, nature!
You are awesome!
How to cure a tree!
Just a polar bear on a stroll!
Bucky! Bucky! Hey! You in there?
We're going to the river, right?
Have those wires always been there?
Where are you? Come on Bucky!
I'm sorry Bjorn! I can't go today!
Where are you?
What do you think you're doing?
Stop that this instant! I mean it! Bucky!
Oh!
Myself!
You say you're hurt, huh?
Oh!
What about the tree?
What?
The apple tree?
Like, what about it?
It's only a tree, right?
A tree is a living thing!
It feels pain too, you know!
Why are you torturing it?
Me?
Torturing?
How?
There's been no torture!
I'm setting up the internet, dude!
Can you just imagine the entire world at our fingertips?
All the latest information in the entire world!
And it's mine for the browsing!
Uh, you're hurting the tree for the sake of internet, huh?
What happens if the tree dies?
This is only a tree, Bjorn!
We have a forest full of them, see?
What's your problem?
Just watch!
When I am through, I'll show you the whole wide world!
So be able to see what our forest looks like from space!
I don't want to see a tree suffer like this!
Not even from space!
You've hurt the poor thing!
And now it feels bad!
Bjorn, you are one odd bear!
I'm attempting to drag you into the current millennium!
All that you seem to be concerned with are some silly trees!
I'm not interested in the kind of progress that causes any trees to suffer!
You can do your internetting without me!
Why was Bjorn that upset?
I've just made this forest so much cooler!
By far!
It's really working!
I'm a genius!
They should call me Albert Einstein!
Home sweet home!
Whoa!
Bjorn sweet Bjorn!
What's he doing?
Poor thing!
Hello, Bjorn!
Are you alright?
Are you still mad at me?
I'm not mad, Bucky!
But you have a growl face!
Well, I'm worried about this poor apple tree!
I've given it a lot of water!
But it's still not looking any better!
So why not just find the right way to fix the tree?
You're an expert on branches and leaves and dirt and all that stuff!
Bjorn, I'll help in any way that I can!
Just let me know what to do!
I'm pretty darn good!
And I'm going to find the right way to fix the tree!
You're an expert on branches and leaves and dirt and all that stuff!
Bjorn, I'll help in any way that I can!
Just let me know what to do!
I'm pretty darn good at everything!
Listen, you don't understand!
The apple tree is a living thing!
It can't just be repaired!
It needs to be treated so that it can heal!
You need to heal a tree!
But you're not certain how!
When there's something that you need to learn, you just have to ask!
The apple tree is a living thing.
It can't just be repaired.
It needs to be treated so that it can heal.
You need to heal a tree, but you're not certain how.
When there's something that you need to learn,
you just have to ask.
And you know where you can find out the answer
to pretty much any question?
Wait for it.
On the internet.
There, it's really easy, see?
Eureka!
Ha ha ha!
Ladder time!
Yeah!
Get these out of your way and tape!
Ooh!
Yeah!
Uh!
Catch!
Nailed it!
Oh yeah!
Incoming!
Looking good!
All right!
Nice work!
Thanks!
It looks so much better than before, right?
It will heal in no time.
What a relief!
What did I tell you, Bjorn?
What would we have done if we hadn't had the internet?
You must see now, it's wonderful, the way that scientific progress can improve our lives.
You're right.
But from now on, can we progress without causing harm to the living things around us?
Like trees, or flowers, or ferns.
Let's just not harm nature at all.
Ever.
Period.
Or else, we won't have anything nice to look at from space.
You look very handsome from space, by the way.
Harvest Hero!
Geek!
Check!
Hi!
Okay, this is incredibly important.
High finance here.
And here, here, here, here, here.
Now I'll rock the world by planting strawberries.
Oh, yeah, I'm cool.
Who's the best?
I'm the best.
Bucky, are you in there?
Come on, it's a beautiful day out here.
I'm coming.
I'm just so busy.
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you in three days now.
We have so much stuff to do.
You know it.
That's why I don't have time for this.
Dude, I have more work than I can handle.
It never ever stops and my back kind of hurts a little.
Huh?
I've got pumpkins to double click.
My strawberries all need de-weedification.
Oh, come inside and I can show you my amazing farm.
Harvest hero, level 26, watch and learn.
Mmm, tools.
Shovel.
Go, beets.
Yes.
Winning.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
Harvest, harvest.
Isn't that just the greatest?
But it's just not, well, none of it's real.
It's way better than real life.
When you hit level five, you get farmer armor.
Then no matter what they stack up against you, you can handle it.
It's intense having all this responsibility.
I don't have time for all this nonsense.
My cauliflower is calling.
Level 27, look out.
Let's go.
Strawberry de-weedification?
Pumpkins aren't supposed to be clicked.
Pumpkins are supposed to be picked.
Which Bucky used to know.
Hmm?
Oh, wait a minute.
Ah, I have a plan.
The very newest game, you say?
Uh-huh.
It just came out today.
It's what they call a virtual reality game.
What does that mean?
It means that the game plays and looks like you're really inside of it.
The entire game feels super real.
And it's so virtual, like you can actually eat the strawberries.
Dude, I've got to try this.
Why am I not playing it?
Come on, where am I going to get to play?
The waiting is too much.
Put this on.
Virtual eyeball interface.
Finger sockets.
Oh, yeah, this is wicked.
This is the Game Gear?
Of course it is.
And now you can turn around.
It's just, I can't believe this is a video game.
The graphics are awesome.
Let me play.
How do you work it?
Where's the controller?
Forget about controllers.
You've got goggles for a screen.
It's got built-in controllers, and they're called your hands.
You walk toward an object and just try and interact with it.
Just like reality.
The virtual baskets are right over there.
It had a real taste.
A yummy one.
This game is fantastic.
All right, let's do this.
Come on, game.
Let's see if you can keep up with me.
Whoa!
That was fun, right?
And you just wanted to sit home double-clicking all day.
Well, who knew you had such an awesome game?
Though I wish the reality of my achy sore back was only virtual.
Maybe if you keep coming outside and playing my game, you'll master it.
And then it won't hurt so much.
Thank you so much, Bjorn.
Good times.
Don't forget to hit save.
I don't want to lose my progress.
I'm going inside to get a little high-quality time in standby mode.
That's gamer talk for a nap.
An actual real nap in my real bed.
A journey!
Good morning, Bjorn!
What are you doing?
Lucky, hi there.
I'm just getting stuff ready to go.
You mean, you're going on a trip?
Can I come, too?
Why not?
Come on along.
I just love to travel the world, but not on foot.
Walking's too slow.
Plus, you can't carry enough stuff.
Plus, you don't see a lot.
Plus, plus, you can get lost.
We won't get lost when I bring this compass with us.
Awesome!
I've got an idea.
Rope, please tell me you have some.
Excellent.
That'll work.
Come over to my place in the morning and bring your stuff.
Time to be awesome!
Hi, Bucky.
Oh, wait a minute.
What's floating in your yard?
It's for us.
A hot air balloon for our trip.
Ugh.
Come on.
Climb on board.
It's time for us to fly.
I don't think I'll be traveling by air.
No way.
I am not a flying bear.
Why not?
The balloon will carry us and all our stuff,
and there's no chance we'll get lost
because we can see everything from up here.
Well, even if you're right about all that,
it's bad weather for flying today.
Uh, I get it.
You're afraid of flying, right?
What?
I am not afraid of flying.
Are you sure?
Ugh!
Problem!
Bjorn! Bjorn!
I'm really scared, Bjorn!
Ugh!
Hey!
Bucky!
Please, do something, Bjorn!
Help me!
Whoa!
Ugh!
Hang on!
It's a hurricane!
I hate flying!
I'm not loving it either!
Whoa!
Ow!
Ugh!
Listen!
Turn us around, Bjorn!
How?
It's your runaway balloon!
You're supposed to be steering it!
Yikes!
Ouch!
My scarf!
Bucky!
Whoa!
You gotta grab that thing!
Come on!
Grab onto that tower!
What?
Ah!
Electric lines!
Whoa!
Look!
Ducks!
Help us, duckies!
Bucky!
We're flying south, I think!
I haven't ever been this way before!
Oh, much longer are we gonna fly, Bjorn!
Long as this big, strong wind blows, we're gonna keep on flying!
Sorry, house on a stick!
I always wanted to ride this!
Yeah!
Aw!
It's spinning fast!
Hold your breath!
Help us, you two!
Whoa!
Look at the cool crane!
Watch out!
Mountain!
Correction!
Volcano!
Why are we still flying?
Yeah, you were right.
Balloon travel was a bad call.
I guess that we better walk home.
But where's home?
We've flown so far, I don't know the way back.
Well, I don't know how to get back.
Don't you have your fancy compass?
Well, yeah.
Only it's still inside my backpack, which is back at your house.
Ugh!
What are we gonna do about this?
I wanna go home!
Bucky, guess what?
I think you were right, my friend.
We can travel in this balloon of yours.
Because I just had a great idea!
That was some great thinking, Bjorn!
This is a great view, just lovely.
Don't forget that I need directions.
Mm, do your job!
Go left!
Good.
I see our volcano over there.
Turn to the right now, then straight ahead.
You're doing great.
Come on, let's switch jobs, so I can do some flying too, Buck.
Is it just me, or have I been pulling a lot longer than you did?
Bjorn?
Ooh, my scarf!
Oh, look out!
We're back at all those wires!
Keep to the right!
Yeah!
Oh!
Hey!
There's your house!
Hooray!
We made it!
Yeah.
Traveling is pretty awesome.
Let's get lost up north tomorrow.
Let's what?
Bjorn, why are you laughing?
I'm serious!
You can see everything from up here.
There's a reason bears don't have wings, right?
Star Story!
Big Dipper!
Ursa Major Great Bear!
What a kick!
Ursa Minor Little Bear!
Whoa, yeah!
Cassiopeia!
Bucky!
Enough reading!
Let's go and play!
I can't now!
Sorry, Bucky!
I'm supposed to study!
Ursa Major Great Bear!
Ursa Minor Little Bear!
The Atlas of the Stars, huh?
Why do you want to learn about the stars?
Polar bears all have to really know every single constellation in the sky!
Well, a book won't do it.
You need to be looking at the stars in real life, Bjorn.
And you can't see them in the day.
Well, at night I can't read the Atlas, and I get really snoozy-woozy.
stars. Polar bears all have to really know every single constellation in the sky.
Well, a book won't do it. You need to be looking at the stars in real life, Bjorn.
And you can't see them in the day. Well, at night, I can't read the Atlas, and I get really snoozy-woozy.
You need to visit a planetarium. Do what? You know, the building where you can look at the stars
whenever you want to, even in the daytime? And do planetariums just grow in the forest?
Um, not really. Well, I guess I'll have to learn the stars by using the book.
You know what? It so happens that the world's greatest planetarium is right in my own cabin!
Or it will be really soon!
I need this for something. Give me half an hour, then come see. I'm a genius!
Time to be awesome!
Big dipper goes here! Fancy glass! Teacup! This is fun! I'm making constellations, baby!
Tree stand! Bowl! Hammer thing! Bucky, you are the coolest friend ever! Yeah!
Hey there, Bjorn! You got here right on time! Come in! Welcome to the Buckyway Galaxy!
Ooh, it's a planetary!
Ooh!
Ah!
Nice try, dude, but there's no polar bear constellation. Seems like you'd know that.
This is a planetarium, is it? What's going on with the ropes everywhere?
Just ignore that. All the other stuff's what you're here to see. Bjorn Bear, come on down! Prepare to have your mind blown!
Just over here is Ursa Major, the Great Bear Pot! It's totally just like the real thing.
Almost exactly, kinda. Up here's the Great Cup. And down here's the Great Broken Cup.
All right, maybe that's not a real constellation.
Uh, how come you hung a hammer? Well, you see, so it occurred to me. There's so many stars, there's gotta be one hammer constellation up there!
I give you nail hit us major! So I made a few up. It's cool though, right? It fills an open space!
Huh? Bjorn, wait! Where are you going? What's wrong?
Bjorn, are you upset or something?
Hey, listen. I can take the hammer down if that's what's wrong. Although it is pretty bangin', if I do say so myself.
There's not a hammer constellation in the sky. Uh, I can fix everything, you know. Make sure it's super accurate so you can study the stars for real.
I'm better off studying out here. Thanks a lot, but your planetarium just isn't my...
Please tell me you see those lights. Look at that! Fireflies! Isn't it pretty?
I wish my behind glowed like that.
Wow, that looks like the Big Dipper! I think it actually looks closer to the Great Bear!
Hmm, Cassiopeia! Hey, just like you said, Bjorn, that you wanted to learn about constellations out here?
Well, that's just what's happening. Nature's showing us all the constellations.
See? That looks like the constellation Leo Minor, Bucky. Nice kitty!
And that's Pisces. Something's fishy about that one.
There's Perseus! Hey, Skyman!
And Orion! Hey, other Skyman!
That looks like Scorpio! That is a big scorpion!
And there's Aquarius! You're spilling your water, dude!
Ooh, there's the Milky Way!
Owl said it isn't the Milky Way. Instead, it's a meteor shower that's learned to dance and do tricks!
That shows how well you understand owl language. What it really said was,
we should all be in bed now, because it's quite late.
Well then, I'll say good night, Bjorn, my friend. Try not to let that hammer fall on your head.
Hahaha!
The best reminder!
Howdy!
Yeah!
Good afternoon, Bucky!
What in the world is this? A doorbell or something?
It's a reminder, not a doorbell. You remember how we made plans to go fishing early tomorrow morning?
Well, I tied a bunch of knots to remind myself to remember not to forget. It's something we always did up north.
Okay, it's not supposed to do that.
That system sounds unreliable. Never fear! I'm going to invent a reliable mechanical reminder system!
We'll remember everything!
Great! But Bucky, please, just remember not to forget our trip!
Time to get my genius on!
Eureka!
Lunch time!
Time to clean!
Time to work out!
Fishing trip!
It works!
Awesome!
All right!
Yeah!
La la la la!
I am one with nature. I am a peaceful bear. A peaceful, peaceful bear. Growl...
Bjorn!
Whoa!
It's so great! Yay! I've done it!
Bjorni, prepare to be amazed! My remind-o-matic works great! Here, let me show you!
Are you excited? Because you absolutely should be!
Watch this! I'll have the remind-o-matic remind Chiki that it's time to eat lunch!
It's so user-friendly that even a bird brain can understand it!
You may want to sit down. This is going to be very exciting!
Wow! Chiki must have been really hungry!
Ta-da! Isn't my remind-o-matic amazing? I'll never ever forget anything now!
What is next on my schedule?
Aha! Time for tea time! Thanks, remind-o-matic!
Being a genius rocks!
Ah! There Bucky goes again!
It's so very tea time!
Ah! Oh goodness! It's time for cleaning!
Long time since I cleaned up!
Huh! Whoa! What now?
Huh?
Huh! It's garden time!
Ah! Huh? Wash!
Huh? Iron? Huh? Time to cook! Time to snack! Time to home! Workout time!
Workout time! Play outside!
Don't forget! Eat! Wash up!
Weed the garden! Sleep! Watch Bearball!
Eat! Never forget!
Eat! Clean! Sleep!
Exercise! All the things!
Remember all the things!
All the things!
Dream!
Drool! Snore!
It's time to what?
I thought it was time to sleep!
Oh, that's right!
It's time for me to turn over!
Quiet!
I can remember to dream on my own!
I can't remember why I built you in the first place!
I'm done! Remind me to throw you away!
Just stop that!
Remind me to forget you!
Good riddings!
Now what was I gonna do?
Good morning!
This reminded me to tell you that it's time to head to the fishing hole!
Hey!
Whatever became of your remind-a-tronic thing, huh?
Trust me on this one!
We're better off forgetting all about that silly thing!
But those reminder-naughts of yours really are a clever idea!
Know what, Bucky?
What?
The most important reminders aren't here, you see!
They're down here!
Well, I'll certainly never forget my best friend!
So, have those reminder-naughts ever woken you up in the middle of the night?
We'll see you next time!
Bye!