Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Insomnia!
Could this get any worse?
Are you kidding me?
Shh! Nobody cares who!
Go away, world!
Stop it!
Ignore it! Just ignore it!
Gotcha! Now shh! I mean it!
I mean it!
Nooo!
Bjorn! Bjorn! Bjorn!
Hey! It's me! Bucky!
Hey Buck! What's going on?
Oh! Morning Bjorn! I can't sleep because I've got no sleepnia!
Insomnia! That's what they call it! Go take a nap! Come back this afternoon and we'll talk about why you can't sleep or whatever then!
How am I supposed to take a nap if I can't sleep!
Well, you've got a point there!
Well, let's solve your problem together and figure out why you're having this insomnia!
To start, tell me everything you did yesterday!
Yesterday? Hang on!
Uh...
In the morning I did some pretty important high-tech research!
A little light farming!
A lot of high-level brain stuff!
Like most days! It's pretty taxing!
Then, after lunch, some moderate to heavy farming!
With yoga on the side!
Then, after some advanced gravity experiments, I invented a whole new way to use a chair!
Oh! Then finally, I thought of two rhymes for the word orange!
But I didn't have anything to write them down with, so I forgot them!
Yeah! Uh-huh! So you just played farm hero all day long!
That pretty much covers it, yes!
Well, I was gonna do more, and then I just didn't!
Well, I do know one cure for insomnia, but I left it under this big pile of firewood!
Can you help find it?
Easy McPeasy!
Not really seeing anything under here!
Maybe it's under this pile!
Or these piles!
Keep looking!
You're doing great, Bucky!
Hey! What's up? Where's your cure?
It's not here!
Well, that's weird! I was sure it was there!
What if it's lost in all that big, tall grass?
Right! So where's the lawnmower?
I was hoping for the kind you ride on!
Oh well, this will work just fine!
Still no sign of a cure!
Keep looking! It's gotta be somewhere!
Nothing! Nada! Squat!
Well...
Well, what?
Now that I'm remembering, that insomnia cure could have fallen from my pocket while I was planting trees!
Wanna check?
Please!
Is it under that log?
Or by the fence, maybe?
Keep looking!
If I look any harder, my eyes will explode!
Yeah, it's under the log!
Or in the hedge!
There!
Hey!
I definitely had it in the flower bed, maybe!
Or was it in the leaves?
Or the dock that isn't there yet!
And did you check the Zen rock garden?
Or under my dirty dishes?
Oh!
Where oh where could it be?
While you're checking the roof, can you install this pinwheel?
Nice!
Thanks!
So is it up there?
I can't believe we still haven't found your insomnia medicine after looking all that time!
It's mega extra lost!
Phew!
I'm so tired!
I'm sleepy!
I'll get some sleep and then we can look for the insomnia cure again in the morning!
Why bother with that?
A hard day's work is the best cure for insomnia at night!
Makes sense!
Hope I can find that no sleep me a cure when I wake up!