Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Gardeners!
Hey there, Bjorn!
So, why are you throwing all these seeds around?
Hey, Bucky! Good morning!
I'm not throwing them around, I'm planting a vegetable garden
It's going to be completely organic!
So what does that mean? Uh, what's the word? Floorpanic?
It's where...
What?
You scatter your seeds around and then let nature do the rest
Completely organic, yeah!
There's just no way you can leave this stuff to nature
You need to be technological!
I'm talking about civilization!
Hm? Hm? Huh?
Hi Bjorn!
Hi there Bucky! What's happening?
Morning, Franny! Hi! What's up?
We're both planting vegetable gardens
Bjorn will do his organic thing while I use technology!
That's spectacular! I'm off to pick blackberries! Later!
I'm gonna be like the greatest gardener in the history of gardens!
Genius time, farmer style!
Behold! The Farminatortron Omaticizer!
So, where do I want to plant all these seeds? I feel the need...
The need for seed! I will make the planet feed me!
There! All planted!
What's step two?
Right! Water time!
Whoa!
Well...
Looks like it's clearing up!
Bjorn, hey!
What are all these green things over here?
I don't think they're vegetables
Actually, they're weeds
They won't cause problems
They're harmless
The weeds are also part of...
The organic world
Well, you might not mind
But I don't want any weeds in...
My garden!
Now I feel the need...
To weed!
Take that, silly weeds!
Very, very, quite contrary!
Let...
My...
Garden...
Grow!
Huzzah!
Who are...
These little guys?
Calm down!
They're harmless insects!
Don't worry!
They don't interfere with my garden at all!
Part of nature, right?
Well, they sure interfere with...
My garden!
Chickie!
Attack the bugs!
Hmm...
Nature will straighten everything out itself!
Think what you like!
My garden's gonna get lots of fertilizer!
Huh?
Hi there!
I brought you some blackberries, guys!
How are your gardens doing?
Look!
Mine has no weeds!
Mine has no insects!
And lots of rocking fertilizer!
So fertile!
That's technology!
Franny, hey!
Do you wanna take a look at my garden?
No chemicals at all!
Organic!
Nature's way!
Organic's awesome!
Really cool, Bjorn!
And yours is cool, Bucky!
But where are your crops?
They're somewhere in here!
I mean, they must be in here somewhere, right?
I just have to find them!
Hold on!
I know they're close by!
Wait!
Well?
Crops incoming!
Where are the tomatoes?
Uh, they should be here!
I just need to look for them!
Uh, there!
Just come on!
Hey!
I found one!
Well?
They're not big!
Bjorn, this is all your fault!
And why is it my fault?
I'll tell you why!
Cause your weeds are everywhere!
So?
What do my weeds have to do with anything?
Hey, guys?
What if you two take a step back?
Oh!
What do my weeds have to do with anything?
Hey, guys!
What if you two take a step back?
Oh!
I'll step back!
And see if you put your cute heads together!
You can figure this out!
I'm not sure!
But thanks for your input!
I should get going!
Bye, guys!
Well, so?
You wanna try this?
Try this what?
Combining our different ways!
We could try it, but there can't be any weeds!
That's fine!
And maybe a bit less cannons and screaming!
Look what we did!
It's better to work together than apart!
Don't you think, Bucky?
Duh!
We actually make a pretty good team, the two of us!
Dude!
We should be on TV!
Yeah!