Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
A trip to the stars!
Bjorn! Get up! It's a disaster! Come on!
Bjorn! A star has fallen!
What do you mean? What star? Where did it fall?
Bjorn! Come on! I'll tell you everything on the way!
Remember you were telling me about shooting stars, right?
Well, I was in the woods this morning, just walking, when BAM! There was a star! Shining!
I got real close and I just couldn't believe it!
There! We're here!
Do you know how early it is?
Look at that!
Isn't it awesome?
It really is a star!
I know! That's what I've been saying!
Now, we just have to get it back into outer space!
Who knows? It could be part of a constellation or something!
But Buck, space is a long way up! How will we get the star back up there?
Duh! We'll build a spaceship!
Rockets are easy McPeasy to build!
Excuse me! Pardon me! Big fat genius coming through!
Friends, I give you the great, super-mcduperific, rocket jet-o-matic R-Infinity Space Wagon!
Applause would be appropriate!
Hmm, uh, don't rockets generally fly kinda up?
Huh?
Uh, right!
That's more like it!
So that's our rocket!
We've just gotta build it now!
Let's get to it!
We can do this!
It's not rocket science!
Oh, except it is!
Ha ha ha!
Hey guys, by any chance have you seen-
Oh, Franny! Hi there!
Do you like our rocket?
Hey, Franny!
It's big!
Uh, where's the door?
Uh, uh, coming right up!
Ha ha!
We should return the star before sunset.
Well in that case, I guess we better hurry!
Start the countdown!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One and three quarters!
Nine and a half!
Now!
I probably should've gone to the toilet first.
first. Did we do it? We actually did it. We're space bears. It's so awesome. So
that's what space looks like. I thought it would be taller. So should we put the
star back now?
I said the star, not chicky, dude. My bad. I mixed the levers up. This is so cool.
Star light, star bright, we hope this sets things right. Now it's time to head
home. Take care of yourself, beautiful little star. Make a wish. Yeah, this has been a wonderful
day. What a terrible day. What? Franny, what's wrong? It's just that I lost an earring
somewhere in the forest and I haven't been able to find it. What did it look like? We'll
help you find it right now. It's just like this one, shiny and star shaped. Oh my, I think
that your star earring is one of those up there. Yeah, where? In the sky. We just took it up
there in our rocket. Guess now there's an earring constellation. Well, I guess it's cool that
it will be shining in the night sky now. We should hang this one in space too. Tomorrow we'll fly up together and put it next to the other one. It'll be awesome.
Put it next to the other one. It'll be awesome.