Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
A journey!
Good morning, Bjorn! What are you doing?
Bucky, hi there! I'm just getting stuff ready to go
You mean, you're going on a trip? Can I come too?
Why not? Come on along!
I just love to travel the world, but not on foot
Walking's too slow, plus you can't carry enough stuff, plus you don't see a lot
Plus plus you can get lost!
We won't get lost when I bring this compass with us
Awesome! I've got an idea!
Rope, please tell me you have some!
Excellent! That'll work!
Come over to my place in the morning and bring your stuff!
Time to be awesome!
Hi Bucky!
Oh, wait a minute! What's floating in your yard?
It's for us! A hot air balloon for our trip!
Come on! Climb on board! It's time for us to fly!
I don't think I'll be traveling by air! No way! I am not a flying bear!
Why not? The balloon will carry us and all our stuff and there's no chance we'll get lost because we can see everything from up here!
Well, even if you're right about all that, it's bad weather for flying today!
Ah, I get it! You're afraid of flying, right?
What? I am not afraid of flying!
Are you sure?
Problem!
Bjorn! Bjorn! I'm really scared!
Hey! Bucky!
Please do something, Bjorn! Help me!
Hang on! It's a hurricane!
I hate flying!
I'm not loving it either!
Whoa!
Ow! Ow!
Listen! Turn us around, Bjorn!
How? It's your runaway balloon!
You're supposed to be steering it!
Yikes!
Ouch!
My scarf!
Bucky!
Bucky! You gotta grab that thing! Come on! Grab onto that tower!
What?
Ah! Electric lines!
Shocking!
Look! Ducks! Help us, duckies!
Bucky! We're flying south, I think!
I haven't ever been this way before!
How much longer are we gonna fly, Bjorn?
Long as this big strong wind blows, we're gonna keep on flying!
Sorry, house on a stick!
I always wanted to ride this!
Yeah!
Aw!
It's spinning fast!
Hold your breath!
Help us, you two!
Whoa! Look at the cool crane!
Watch out! Mountain!
Correction! Volcano!
Why are we still flying?
Yeah, you were right. Balloon travel was a bad call.
I guess that we better walk home.
But where's home?
We've flown so far, I don't know the way back!
Well, I don't know how to get back!
Don't you have your fancy compass?
Well, yeah.
Only it's still inside my backpack, which is back at your house!
Ugh!
What are we gonna do about this? I wanna go home!
Bucky, guess what?
I think you were right, my friend!
We can travel in this balloon of yours!
Because I just had a great idea!
That was some great thinking, Bjorn!
This is a great view, just lovely!
Don't forget that I need directions!
Do your job!
Go left!
Good! I see our volcano over there!
Turn to the right now, then straight ahead!
You're doing great!
Come on, let's switch jobs, so I can do some flying too, Buck!
Is it just me, or have I been pulling a lot longer than you did?
Bjorn?
Ooh, my scarf!
Oh, look out!
We're back at all those wires!
Keep to the right!
Yo!
Bucky!
Your other right!
Oh!
Hey!
There's your house!
Hooray!
We made it!
Yeah!
Traveling is pretty awesome!
Let's get lost up north tomorrow!
Let's what?
Bjorn?
Why are you laughing?
I'm serious!
Bears don't have wings, right?