Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Star Story!
Big Dipper, Ursa Major Great Bear
What a kick!
Ursa Minor Little Bear
Cassiopeia
Bucky!
Enough reading, let's go and play!
I can't now, sorry Bucky
I'm supposed to study
Ursa Major Great Bear, Ursa Minor Little Bear
The Atlas of the Stars, huh?
Why do you want to learn about the stars?
Polar bears all have to really know every single constellation in the sky
Well, a book won't do it
You need to be looking at the stars in real life, Bjorn
And you can't see them in the day
Well at night, I can't read the Atlas
And I get really snoozy woozy
You need to visit a planetarium!
Do what?
What?
You know, the building where you can look at the stars whenever you want to, even in the daytime
And do planetariums just grow in the forest?
Um, not really
Well I guess, I'll have to learn the stars by using the book
Hmm
You know what?
It so happens that the world's greatest planetarium is...
Right in my own cabin!
Or I will be really soon!
I need this for something
Give me half an hour, then come see
I'm a genius!
Time to be awesome!
Big Dipper goes here!
Fancy glass!
Teacup!
This is fun!
I'm making constellations, baby!
Tree stand!
Bowl!
Hammer thing!
Bucky, you are the coolest friend ever!
Yeah!
Hey there, Bjorn!
You got here right on time!
Come in!
Welcome to the Bucky Way galaxy!
Ooh!
It's a planetary...
Nice try, dude!
But there's no polar bear constellation!
Seems like you'd know that!
This is a planetarium, is it?
What's going on with the ropes everywhere?
Just ignore that!
All the other stuff's what you're here to see!
Bjorn Bear, come on down!
Prepare to have your mind blown!
Just over here is Ursa Major, the great bear pod!
It's totally just like the real thing!
Almost exactly kinda!
Up here's the great cup!
And down here's the great broken cup!
Alright, maybe that's not a real constellation!
Uh, how come you hung a hammer?
Well, you see, so it occurred to me!
There's so many stars, there's gotta be one hammer constellation up there!
I give you nail hit us major!
So I made a few up!
It's cool though, right?
It fills an open space!
Huh?
Bjorn, wait!
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
Bjorn?
Are you upset or something?
Hey listen!
I can take the hammer down if that's what's wrong!
Although it is pretty bangin', if I do say so myself!
There's not a hammer constellation in the sky!
Uh, I can fix everything, you know!
Make sure it's super accurate so you can study the stars for real!
I'm better off studying out here!
Thanks a lot, but your planetarium just isn't my...
Please tell me you see those lights!
Look at that!
Fireflies!
Isn't it pretty?
I wish my behind glowed like that!
Wow!
That looks like the big dipper!
I think it actually looks closer to the great bear!
Mmm, Cassiopeia!
Hey!
Just like you said, Bjorn!
That you wanted to learn about constellations out here?
Well, that's just what's happening!
Nature's showing us all the constellations!
See?
That looks like the constellation Leo Minor, Bucky!
Nice kitty!
And that's Pisces!
Something's fishy about that one!
There's Perseus!
Hey, Skyman!
And Orion!
Hey, other Skyman!
That looks like Scorpio!
That is a big scorpion!
And there's Aquarius!
You're spilling your water, dude!
Ooh!
There's the Milky Way!
Owl said it isn't the Milky Way!
Instead, it's a meteor shower that's learned to dance and do tricks!
That shows how well you understand owl language!
What it really said was, we should all be in bed now, because it's quite late!
Well then, I'll say goodnight Bjorn, my friend!
Try not to let that hammer fall on your head!
Hehehe!
The End
Cars