Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
La la la la
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
La la la la
When you spend it with a friend just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky
The home stretch
This is awesome
Yeah
Oh, guys, we should totally make our own racing cars, am I right?
Andy's off
I'm building the super fastest car with super strength and super muscle
Zoom across the finish line
Engine, gas, super turbo, vroom!
Hit the brakes!
What?
We don't want a plain regular smoggy car with oil drips and all that exhaust
We should build a whole new kind of car
One that runs on pure clean fuel
Like the wind, for instance
And we could just float like clouds
What?
Cars should be as fast as lightning!
Engine, gas, super turbo!
We need to build a proper racing car!
But
My wind car would be pretty quick
Let's make my wind powered race car
Listen, guys
Why don't we just make both of them?
And then we can race the cars against each other
What do you think?
Should we race?
Totally
Yeah
The racers pull up to the starting line
On the right, you will see in the red helmet, Thunder Bucky
In his sweet super ride, the SKT 4 million trillion kajillion
The fastest most powerful race car in the universe!
Ha ha!
And on the left, you'll see in the blue helmet, Bjorn Free
In his clean and lightweight and eco-friendly new vehicle, the Speedy Cloud!
Gentlemen, start your engines!
Ready, get set, race!
Eat my dust, twin boy!
Whatcha doin'?
Hmm?
I'm riding the wind, like the wind!
Vroomity vroom! Vroom vroom vroom!
So whoosh!
I guess, maybe
Vroom! Vroom vroom! Screech!
Yeah!
I've gotta be the fastest bear in the world!
Vroom!
Vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom vroom v
with my awesome race car,
whereas my eco-friendly wind machine
is absolutely immune to the hiccups.
Oh.
Oh, I think the wind stopped.
I could use some eco-help here.
My goodness, nobody even made it
across the finish line, guys.
Well, if there's no wind,
there's no eco-speed.
It just needs some wind.
All right, then.
Bucky, what do you have?
A fan.
It blows air in one direction.
Just like, oh, maybe the wind.
And who might need some wind?
Do I need to spell it out?
Franny's right.
Let's work together to make wind.
But of course, Fran, you're a genius.
I can't wait to see the speedy cloud four-gajillion-trillion-million in action.
ahead.
oh.
Ha.
Haha.
Hm.
Hahahaha.
Stere to the left!
Aye, aye, Captain!
Woo-hoo!
Yay!
It's awesome!
Yeah!
Taking walks and playing games
When there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs
Or reading books together
Friends together
Or inventing super mega awesome
One-of-a-kind race cars together
Everything together