Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Just the right size!
Nice try! Almost!
I'm telling you, the trolls are a trillion percent real
Sure they are!
They're as big as mountains
And terribly mean and ugly
Hey Franny, why aren't you eating cherries? Don't you like them?
I love them, but I can't reach them
Alrighty then! You know, this tree would barely come up to a troll's knees
You guys never change! You care more about trolls or whatever than me!
Don't be silly! We care about you, Franny!
Hey, trolls don't even exist! But you're completely real!
Oh, Franny! I think I know what can be done to help you!
Hey, we're gonna build Franny something! A fancy ladder just for her so she can reach the cherries!
Awesome plan!
My workshop is out of bounds for little kids!
Hey, why don't you go swing or something? We'll be right back!
Bjorn, close the curtains! This is gonna be awesome!
No little kids! That's all I ever hear!
I'm sick of being little!
Flying through the sky
Like a furry butterfly
She's so cool, I'll tell you why
She's Franny the Cool Big Fox!
I am!
Ladders are okay! But this'll be way cool!
Phew!
Well, it's done! The larger charger!
Hey!
Where's Fran?
The trolls ate her!
Uh, she's probably picking flowers somewhere!
Or trying to pick cherries! Let's go find her!
New invention?
Larger charger, huh?
I wonder if it'll make me bigger!
Hey! What happened to me?
Where could Franny have possibly gone?
That girl's always so much trouble!
It's a...
Troll!
Not a troll!
It's Franny, guys!
Franny, guys!
Troll!
Guys!
Up here!
I know you're in there somewhere!
Eeny, meeny, miny, miny, yo!
This is getting silly!
Come here!
Look, it's...
Franny!
There!
So you used the larger charger without even asking first!
I just wanted to be big enough so you guys would have to notice me!
Well, you're certainly hard to miss like this!
Don't be upset,
Don't be upset, Franny!
We'll think of a way to help!
I don't wanna be a troll!
Whoa!
Just stop crying!
You're acting like a big baby!
I can't help it!
I wanna be little, like I was before!
I don't wanna be big!
I don't wanna be a whale pox!
Franny!
Huh?
We made something so you won't be too small anymore!
Bucky, it's time!
Get Franny's big surprise, please!
Oh, please!
Just not the larger charger!
I've never heard of that!
But this is yours!
To get at High Branches, the Super Climatron!
You made me a ladder of my very own?
A ladder?
This is no ordinary ladder!
It's a Super Climatron with an advanced platform system
and dual bear transport action!
So, Franny, you can pick all the yummy cherries that you'd like now!
Come try it out!
Yeah! Climatronic, baby!
Oh, I'm telling you!
The trolls are absolutely for real!
Uh-huh!
Yeah, sure they are!
I suppose that trolls can just rip trees right from the ground, too!
Yeah, of course!
Silly bears!
I just adore you!