Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Dragon Heroes!
Once upon a time, in a forest far, far away
Two brave warriors set out to rescue a princess
From the clutches of a terrible dragon
They were called Sir Buxalot, the Bravish
And Bjorn Dolph, the Great Wizard
And this is their tale
Another actual tale, their story!
Aha! These are fresh dragon tracks!
Good thing I'm so brave-ish!
The beautiful princess lived in the very heart of the forest
In a cold, lonely tower
Which the dragon guarded day and night
Princess here! Hey knights!
Called the princess with all her might
And our heroes knew they must act
I'll construct an attack tower
You sneak around the back and magic up some rain!
Let's dig a pit to trap the dragon
And then we can lure him into it
There isn't time for that! We must act at once!
They agreed with a lofty quintet
Well, this and that and that shall fit together!
And make a super-advanced catapult-a-torn-o-matic!
Meanwhile, elsewhere in the forest...
Rain, rainy, rain, rain...
Stop being such a pain and just rain!
Pears?
This isn't right at all!
Dragonus Disappearance!
Uh, what the...
It's a fish?
Where'd my sword go?
Oops!
Oh, Sir Buxolot!
I'm terribly sorry, friend
Maybe it's allergic to seafood
It wasn't
The princess had no idea what her rescuers thought they were doing
Wise Björndolf!
Magically transform this stick into a sphere!
Uh-huh!
I hear ya!
Right!
Random stickus!
Other thingus!
Uh...
Yeah!
That'll do!
Huh?
Ah!
Whoa!
Oh!
Ow!
Uh!
Huh?
By all my knightly honor!
Run away!
And the bravest knight and wise wizard embarrass themselves again!
Run!
Huh?
So, where'd this pit come from?
Uh...
I dug it!
But it's not a pit!
It's supposed to be a dragon trap!
Great!
Now the dragon's going to eat us!
And then something unexpected!
But...
What are you doing?
You're not eating us?
Do we look like we taste that bad?
I'm just so happy that my dragon saved you guys!
The princess?
We thought it was you that needed saving!
You were crying out for help, right?
Yes!
I do want your help!
Poor dragon here has stepped on an ouchie burr!
And I can't get it out!
It would be an enormous honor to come to your assistance fair princess!
Wise Bjorn Dolph!
A little help?
And then they held a whopping dandy party!
And that is the very end of the story!
Yes!
Let's go and play knights!
I will be Sir Buxalot the Bravish!
And I'll be the great and wise wizard Bjorn Dolph!
Except my tricks will work!
Well then, I will be the princess!
You should be the dragon!
If I'm the dragon, I'll be barbecuing some knights!
Fine!
Then you can be the princess in the tower!
Let's go!
Adventure is waiting for us!
I hope that adventure brought some snacks!