Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Harvest Hero!
Here, here, here, here, here!
Now I'll rock the world by planting strawberries!
Oh yeah!
I'm cool!
Who's the best?
I'm the best!
Bucky!
Are you in there?
Come on!
It's a beautiful day out here!
I'm coming!
I'm just so busy!
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you in three days now!
We have so much stuff to do!
You know it!
That's why I don't have time for this!
Dude, I have more work than I can handle!
It never ever stops and my back kinda hurts a little!
Huh?
I've got pumpkins to double click!
My strawberries all need de-weedification!
Oh!
Come inside!
And I can show you my amazing farm!
Harvest Hero, level 26, watch and learn!
Hmm, tools!
Shovel!
Go!
Beats!
Yes!
Winning!
Yeah!
Haha!
Oh!
No, no, no, no!
Yes!
Harvest!
Isn't that just the greatest?
Uh-huh!
But it's just not...
Well, none of it's real!
It's way better than real life!
When you hit level five you get farmer armor!
Then no matter what they stack up against you,
you can handle it!
It's intense having all this responsibility!
I don't have time for all this nonsense!
My cauliflower is calling!
Level 27, look out!
Strawberry de-weedification?
Pumpkins aren't supposed to be clicked!
Pumpkins are supposed to be picked!
Which Bucky used to know!
Hmm?
Wait a minute!
Ahh!
I have a plan!
The very newest game you say?
Uh-huh!
It just came out today!
It's what they call a virtual reality game!
What does that mean?
It means that the game plays and looks like you're really inside of it!
The entire game feels super real!
And it's so virtual, like you can actually eat the strawberries!
Dude!
I've gotta try this!
Why am I not playing it?
Come on!
When am I gonna get to play?
The waiting is too much!
Put this on!
Virtual eyeball interface!
Finger sockets!
Aw yeah!
This is wicked!
This is the game gear?
Of course it is!
And now you can turn around!
Wah!
It's just...
I can't believe this is a video game!
The graphics are awesome!
Let me play!
How do you work it?
Where's the controller?
Forget about controllers!
You've got goggles for a screen!
It's got built-in controllers and they're called your hands!
You walk toward an object and just try and interact with it!
Just like reality!
The virtual baskets are right over there!
It had a real taste!
A yummy one!
This game is fantastic!
Alright, let's do this!
Come on game!
Let's see if you can keep up with me!
Ooh!
Aww!
Jackie!
Oh!
Wah!
Whoa!
Ooh!
Oh!
What?
The vocêsatares are uit.
That was fun, right?
And you just wanted to sit home double-clicking all day.
Well, who knew you had such an awesome game?
Though I wish the reality of my achy sore back was only virtual.
Maybe if you keep coming outside and playing my game, you'll master it.
And then it won't hurt so much.
Thank you so much, Bjorn.
Good times. Don't forget to hit save.
I don't want to lose my progress.
I'm going inside to get a little high-quality time in standby mode.
That's gamer talk for a nap.
An actual real nap in my real bed.