Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
I think it's the highest a kite's ever flown ever!
Gosh, it's pretty! Can I have a turn?
Of course, just be sure you hold it real tight
Yeah, sure!
Why is it falling?
The wind died down
Look out for that tree!
Well, that's that
Not on my watch!
I'll get it down!
Ha-ha!
Oh, Bucky?
You might want to back up!
Ha-ha!
The bear!
Touch the sky!
Nope!
That was the sky's fault!
Listen, you have to take your time
Climb slow and steady
Plan each step
This time I'll get it!
I got it! I got it! I got it! I don't!
I'll get it! I'll get it! I'll get it! Come on!
Getting there...
Oh, no, you don't!
Hey, guys, why don't we just leave that one there and make a new one?
No way! Our kite doesn't belong to this tree!
Look, Bjorn's almost got it already!
Hey, Bjorn! No kite ever gets left behind!
I didn't get it down.
All right, we need better equipment.
Tree beat ladder. I'm going up to get our kite back.
Maybe hold the ladder.
Bjorn, I can't quite reach it. I need backup.
Get up here!
Uh-huh. I can almost reach it!
Ugh! Franny, come up here!
We're so close!
Just a teeny bit more. One strand of tail fur!
Just be sure that you hold the ladder steady.
Don't let go!
Hey, Bucky. I was just wondering if all of us are up here, then who's...
I think that I know what our best plan is now.
We just build a new kite?
What?
No.
Now we make a tornado with our lungs.
Blow as hard as you can.
Come on!
Oh, you've got to be kidding me!
All right, guys, maybe we should stop.
You're right.
Throwing sticks is not smart because we might hurt the kite, but I've got the answer.
Friends, I give you the brand-newest incredible awesome invention.
It's the poultry poult.
Hop in, bud.
It's super simple to operate.
All you do is pull the lever.
Good test.
This time we just aim a little better and try again.
Try again.
And again.
So we might have exceeded operational capacity.
The poultry poult is kaput.
You guys, hey, why don't we make an even better kite instead?
Hey, that sounds like a great idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Franny, you're a genius.
It's so pretty.
Can I have a turn?
Of course.
Here it is.
Just try not to let the wind do that again.
Oh, no.
Oh.
I don't like that tree.
So, we just build a new one, right?
You kidding?
I can get it down.
Ha ha!
Here we go again.