Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
How to cure a tree
Just a polar bear on a stroll
Bucky! Bucky, hey! You in there?
We're going to the river, right?
Have those wires always been there?
Where are you? Come on, Bucky!
I'm sorry, Bjorn! I can't go today!
Where are you?
What do you think you're doing?
Stop that this instant! I mean it! Bucky!
Oh!
Ouchie McPainPain! Why are you screaming?
You totally made me hurt myself!
You say you're hurt, huh?
What about the tree?
What? The apple tree? Like, what about it? It's only a tree, right?
A tree is a living thing!
It feels pain too, you know!
Why are you torturing it?
Me? Torturing? How?
There's been no torture! I'm setting up the internet, dude!
Can you just imagine the entire world at our fingertips?
All the latest information in the entire world!
And it's mine for the browsing!
Uh, you're hurting the tree for the sake of internet, huh?
What happens if the tree dies?
This is only a tree, Bjorn! We have a forest full of them, see? What's your problem?
Just watch! When I am through, I'll show you the whole wide world! So be able to see what our forest looks like from space!
I don't want to see a tree suffer like this! Not even from space!
You've hurt the poor thing, and now it feels bad!
Bjorn, you are one odd bear! I'm attempting to drag you into the current millennium!
All that you seem to be concerned with are some silly trees!
I'm not interested in the kind of progress that causes any trees to suffer!
You can do your internetting without me!
Why was Bjorn that upset? I've just made this forest so much cooler! By far!
It's really working!
I'm a genius! They should call me Albert Einstein!
Home sweet home!
Whoa! Bjorn sweet Bjorn! What's he doing?
Poor thing!
Hello Bjorn! Are you alright? Are you still mad at me?
I'm not mad Bucky! Just-
But you have a growl face!
Well, I'm worried about this poor apple tree!
I've given it a lot of water, but it's still not looking any better!
So why not just find the right way to fix the tree?
You're an expert on branches and leaves and dirt and all that stuff!
Bjorn, I'll help in any way that I can! Just let me know what to do! I'm pretty darn good at everything!
Listen, you don't understand! The apple tree is a living thing! It can't just be repaired! It needs to be treated so that it can heal! But I don't know what to do!
So, you need to heal a tree, but you're not certain how!
When there's something that you need to learn, you just have to ask! And you know where you can find out the answer to pretty much any question? Wait for it! On the internet!
There! It's really easy! See? Eureka!
Ladder time! Yeah!
Get these out of your way! And tape! Yeah!
Catch! Nailed it!
Oh yeah!
Incoming!
Looking good!
Alright!
Nice work!
Thanks!
It looks so much better than before, right?
It will heal in no time!
What a relief!
What did I tell you, Bjorn?
What would we have done if we hadn't had the internet?
You must see now! It's wonderful! The way that scientific progress can improve our lives!
You're right!
But from now on, can we progress without causing harm to the living things around us?
Like trees, or flowers, or ferns?
Let's just not harm nature at all! Ever! Period!
Or else, we won't have anything nice to look at from space!
You look very handsome from space, by the way!
By the way!