Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Pirate story!
Lay in a course for home, roared the pirate captain
And a skull and crossbones flag rose atop the main mast
The end! Yeah!
Wow, that's so great! Oh, I want to be a pirate!
Me too! I'll be the pirate captain, and you can be my crew!
Why do you get to be captain? I would be a cool pirate captain!
Ha! You, Bjorn! You're not cut out to be a pirate captain!
I'd be an awesome captain!
No, I'm the captain! No, I'm captain!
You scarvey bear!
Boys, boys! Come on, don't fight!
Look, I baked a nice pie!
Want some!
Franny, can you not see we're in the middle of an important discussion?
Look here, Bjorn! I'm the pirate captain, and that is final!
All right! Captain your ship! I'll just have a ship of my own!
Boys!
Chicky ahoy!
Sweet! Awesome!
Yeah, I am totally a pirate captain!
The king of the seven seas!
Who's there?
Arr! Shiver me timbers! Raise the mizzenmast!
Full speed ahead!
Arr!
Huh?
What is this bottle doing here?
Bottle, aye?
Where'd you come from?
There's something inside!
Ooh! A treasure map!
Blimey! A treasure map!
Well, blow me down!
A circle of grass!
Yo-ho!
A pine tree without branches!
A rock!
Yar!
Aha!
Bucky eye!
That's Captain Bookbeard to you!
Oh, is that so?
Well, I'm Captain Longbjorn Silver!
I have both a parrot and a treasure map to prove it!
No, I'm the captain!
My map is way better than that lame map that you have, fake captain!
Oh, we'll just see about that!
I'll find my treasure before you find your dumb treasure!
I know I'll find mine before you!
There's no way he'll find the treasure first!
Without my new treasure-seagoscope!
All right?
Find some treasure!
Ahoy!
Treasure!
Yeah!
Wait, what?
Curses, it'd be a rock!
Ahoy!
Nah, just an acorn!
Booty, ahoy!
Ah, blast!
It's only a mushroom!
Well, Chickie, according to the treasure map, what we're trying to find should be nearby!
Go look around!
Find the treasure, Chickie!
Find it!
Have you got it?
Did you find it?
No, Chickie, that's a strawberry!
Keep searching!
Not quite!
That's a raspberry!
Try again, please!
Those are pine cones, Chickie!
Whoa!
You are a treasure-seagoscope, not a random wrong stuff-seagoscope!
Find treasure!
You scallywag!
Whoa!
Sorry!
I didn't mean it!
Whoa!
Did you have any luck?
None, did you?
No, sir!
The problem is that this stupid map is useless!
That's right!
Yours and mine both are!
I've searched near every tree and found nothing!
Hey, wait a second!
Take a look, Bjorn!
Bucky!
Are these two halves of one bigger map?
Huh!
So we were looking near the wrong trees!
Arr!
Yo-ho-ho!
So why is that this stupid map is useless?
What?
So why is the ladder here?
Climb up!
I'll hold it steady!
There's something in there!
Oh!
Treasure!
It must be the treasure!
Ha-ha!
Whoa!
Look!
Dude, hi!
I guess that's why they call us pirates!
Ha-ha!
Good one, Buff!
Hey guys!
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh!
Hey, what are you doing here, Franny?
I-
Hang on!
Just listen to this, Franny.
We just found a genuine pirate treasure pie!
I made that pie!
I wanted to play pirates with you guys,
but you were ignoring me.
So I'm the one who drew the treasure map,
just like I'm the one who baked the pie!
Arr!
That's awesome, Franny!
This turned out to be the tastiest pirate story ever!
Isn't that right, Longbjorn Silver?
Yep, you're absolutely correct about that,
my dear Captain Buckbeard!
What happened to our pie?
Bring that back, you rapscallion!