Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
A Cosmic Costume Party!
For New Year's, I'm going to be a princess
Well Bjorn, have you made your costume for the big party yet?
I'm going as a pirate
I bet Bucky's going to show up in that old alien costume he always wears
No I'm not, because I'll be wearing an amazing new alien getup
If you say so, sure
It's the coolest costume ever!
Um, I'll be back soon! Chickie, I've got to make my old alien costume even better!
Chickie!
Oopsie!
I wonder if they have New Year's Eve and costume parties on other worlds
Of course! They have New Year's Eve everywhere! Even on other planets!
You see that?
Huh? Say what?
Uh, never mind
Legal, da-da, blurt!
My costume needs something amazingly cool, but what?
I'll see that!
What do we have here?
Just junk!
Whoa!
Totally perfect!
Time to be awesome!
Almost ready!
Where have you been, Bucky?
And where's your great new alien outfit?
It's coming!
Don't start without me!
Floop!
Deeper!
Turn the lights on now, Bjorn!
Scree-dackle-slee!
Cle-ski!
Bucky!
What an awesome costume!
So cool!
How did you make that?
You really look like a real live alien!
I say that it's time to party!
He-he-he-he-he!
E-he-he!
He-he-he!
Hey, hey, hey!
He-he!
Bucky!
Eye, honey!
He-he-he!
Oh!
Hey, hey!
Ares-y!
Bucky!
He-he-he!
What an awesome costume!
So cool!
How did you make that?
You really look like a real
live alien!
I say that it's time to party!
Narble, Tork, and Wakey!
Narble, Tork, and Lark-Nark!
Huh? Bucky, what's wrong?
He's doing a great job of acting like an alien!
Greetings, Earth Dwellers!
I come in peace and slight dizziness!
Lark-Nark jerks me!
Primitive mammals!
Whoa! I think that that's a real alien!
I am! Pretty groovy, right?
Yes! I am a real-life, actual, bonafide, awesome-sauce alien!
Welcome to Earth, Mr. Alien!
It's wonderful that you decided to come visit us!
Studying life-forms?
Who's this?
Let go of me!
Hey! That thing's mine!
Um, a pair of Bucky's!
There can only be one Bucky! And that's me!
Well, if you're Bucky, who's that guy, huh?
I have no idea!
Hi there! My name is Franny!
What's your name, Mr. Alien?
Activating Talkytron!
A Vico Vrif Poruski!
Habla Espanol!
Greetings, Earthlings!
I came here from the planet Dweebus, but my spaceship has broken down, and I've been unable to repair it!
I wish to return to beautiful Dweebus!
A broken spaceship?
No sweat!
I can fix anything!
You'll be back on Dweebus in no time!
Broken down spaceship?
I know what to do!
Bury that baby in a ton of brain!
Boo!
There's no malfunction that's a match for my IQ!
I'm a hairy fairy genius!
Everybody knows it's true!
LARPUS PROVO NEPRA JUMP JUMP HERE TO MARCO BLINK I'LL PROOVE!
You said it, brother!
All done!
Your ship is completely repaired!
Thanks, dude!
But my accelerator is still missing!
Is this it?
Yes!
That's it!
Ha!
Singety dong!
Thank you, Bucky!
I will never forget you strange creatures!
Are you certain that you have to leave us?
Sadly, yes!
I need to get home for New Years!
Bucky, a token of my thanks!
Thanks very much, my intergalactic friend!
Be careful up there!
Flying through the galaxy and all!
Hop in!
I have time for a quick joy ride!
Spaceship!
Dude!
We're in an alien spaceship for wheelsies!
Are we getting beamed?
We're totally getting beamed!
Goodbye!
Dear Earth friend!
Come visit us again!
Hey!
Happy New Years!
I'm totally dressing as Earth Bucky at this year's costume party!
And I am definitely dressing as an alien again!
Know what?
Me too!
I wonder how they're celebrating New Years on all those far away planets!
Flea, bull, grey!
What's the proofs for Doug?
We go, flabas!
Glur, pose, prom, spunk, me, blub, d'wag!
Videos on the wall!
χx3
GASSE
די
Calls
ơ
mil
Swea
S
Vogs
Pervre