Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
A northern expedition!
This is the life!
Nice day we're having!
The nicest!
It's so hot!
Oh my!
A great day, right?
So very great!
So hot!
Perfect day!
The best!
Huh?
Too hot!
Bjorn, what's with you?
Of course it's hot!
It's summer!
But in the north it's cold!
The whole year round!
Nice and cool!
Snow and icebergs everywhere!
So hey!
Maybe you should take a trip up north then!
Awesome idea!
A northern expedition!
But it's a long way away!
I'd have to prepare and stuff!
We'll get you prepared and stuff!
Trust me!
I'm an expert at everything!
Ha!
You know Bjorn, the north has gotten way norther!
It's colder and bleaker and more dangerous here!
You'll need warm clothes, good skis, party provisions, and…
I don't know…
Snow screen cream?
The north doesn't mess around, my friend!
I'm okay!
Bucky?
I'm not sure about this trip!
I've got your back, Bjorn!
You won't go anywhere…
Until I've trained you!
Just wait…
Hang on!
Be right with ya!
Talk amongst yourselves!
Nearly there now!
I hope you're excited, cause this is gonna be super duper kaplowie wowie!
Everybody, it's my pleasure to present to you at this time…
The one-of-a-kind Northern Expedition Simulator Training Gord!
Thank you, thank you, thank you very much!
Thank you!
Woah!
I'm not so sure about all this, Bucky!
Come on, you'll be fine!
Let's go!
It can strike at any moment!
The whipping wind!
The blinding snow!
That elemental juggernaut!
A northern blizzard!
Feel the frigid frozen fury!
Haha!
Feathers in your face!
Try to keep your footing on those slick, slippery slivers scattered on the sea!
Northern icebergs!
Hey, what are these, Buck?
I'm not sure, but the North can be unpredictable!
You never know what the North's gonna throw at you next!
Dangling tree trunks of icy doom?
It could happen!
And don't forget the thrilling, deadly majesty of the North's countless snow-covered mountains!
Where gravity, physics, and geometry conspire to take you on a pulse-pounding ride that will scare your downy white fur off!
Uh, help?
Bucky, I'm not certain that I want to go on this expedition up north!
Sure you do!
Don't worry!
Thanks to me, you're now completely prepared for your northern expedition!
Well, gosh!
Guess I'll go?
Great!
Safe travels!
Stay warm!
Take lots of pictures!
Um, so, goodbye, I guess?
Yep!
Send us a postcard!
You could maybe just stay, Bjorn!
Is that really an option?
Of course, pal!
What does the North have to offer that we don't have right here?
Icebergs, snow mountains, penguins, frostbite?
We got all that stuff!
Actually, why would you want to leave at all?
I never really wanted to go at all!
Yay!
Bjorn's going to stay!
Now you have your own north that you can share with friends!
Complete with your very own yellow penguin!
Penguin!
Bucky, you do know penguins only live in the south!
Mmm!
No penguins?
That's kind of a rip-off!
Hey, wait!
If you don't have penguins, what do you have?
Absolutely no penguin droppings!
Ha!
Now that is a plus!
Hey, wait!
If you don't have penguins, what do you have?
Absolutely no penguin droppings!
Ha!
Now that is a plus!
concretely no penguin droppings
Ha!
Now that is a plus!