Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Honey Story!
I'll be right there!
Bucky? Franny?
Try a little of my wild berry tea
It's crazy good for you!
Made from raspberries and dewberries and farkleberries
I picked them myself
Thanks a lot Bjorn!
So tasty!
Ugh! It's sour!
You should add some, like, marmalade
Nah, it doesn't need any marmalade
You just need to get used to it!
Oh, add some chocolate!
It does not need chocolate!
Well, then, uh, honey?
You could add that, sure
You know what? I've never tried honey before in my life! Not once!
What? No honey?
We have to fix that!
You're about to take your first step into a yummier world, Franny, my friend!
Well, let's go collect some honey from the bees for you to enjoy!
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh!
I'm not getting stung!
Forget that!
Who needs bees?
I'll make my own honey!
If the bees can do it, so can I!
I can do way better than a bunch of bugs!
Honey!
Making honey!
Now, what am I gonna need?
Not that!
Not that either!
That I will need!
Negative!
Affirmative!
Negatory!
Absolutely!
Nope!
Nope-a-rooney!
No thank you!
Hmm...
This should come in handy!
Alright, then!
Dear bees!
Good day!
Could I, perhaps, have some honey?
Hello?
Oh, that didn't work!
So, plan B!
So, how does the honey-naterizer work, you ask?
Well, it's simple!
Of course, everybody knows honey is made from pollen!
So, we begin with a pollen-gathering device!
Or, pollen-slurp-up-a-naterizer!
Once slurp-up-a-naterized, the pollen dissolves in water and mixes with sugar!
Why sugar?
Because everybody in the world knows that honey's very sweet!
That's right, Chickie!
Time to make the world's first bear honey!
This is very exciting!
Dear bee buddies, please let me take a little bit of your fine honey, and to say thanks, I'll sing you a nice song!
Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather!
Blah!
If there's...
Ouch!
Aaaaaaah!
Rain there singin', wah!
Readin' books together!
Blah!
Whoa!
Every day just has a way.
I'm very sorry, I didn't mean to upset you.
Get along, little horsey upinatorizer, yee-haw!
So, here we go!
Slurp, yes!
Yikes!
Bucky, oh, save me from this army of bees!
Wah, get off that whateverizer and help me, Bucky!
Bjorn, hold on, I'll save you!
Yeah, when, because now would work great for me!
Whoa!
Ugh, phew!
So, you like my honey?
Ha, I'm sure it's great!
Ugh, gross!
That's, like, evil anti-honey!
Oh, my plan like big super-filled plus.
My plan hyper-crashed and burned as well.
All I got was stung all over.
Bjorn, I'm sorry.
It's not smart to get so close to bees.
What did you say?
And what if you didn't have to get close to the bees?
Franny, you're a mega-genius!
I'll be back!
Come on!
Whoa!
Oh!
Ooh!
Okay.
This way the bees won't bother us at all.
You see, Bjorn?
Go left, back to the right, up a little, and we're in!
Yeah!
Now, a little slurp-down-inator-ization, and we are in the honey!
Well, you're right.
Honey is very delicious.
Also, it's nutritious.
Kind of awful.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.