Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Where? Here? Maybe nothing!
What about... here?
Hey, mushrooms! Are you all on vacation or what?
I give up! There are no mushrooms anywhere!
I don't think there ever were! Bjorn and Bucky!
Where'd he go? Who can keep up with that bear?
What are you doing? Earth to the polar bear!
So am I just looking for mushrooms all alone?
You had time to find all those mushrooms and have a dance party too?
Alright Bjorn, tell me how you found them!
Cause I looked everywhere really hard!
And I found none!
I don't really know, Bucky! I'm just totally in tune with nature!
Bjorn and the forest drum to the same beat! And that's how!
But where you come from, there's no forest! Just a lot of snow!
There is snow, yeah! But there's forest too! And animals and the ocean! The north is pretty big!
Question! How do you stock up for the winter up north where the world is frozen?
Mushroom-sickles! Just kidding! We dry fish! And there's juicy walrus steaks and yummy fish oil!
Yummy fish oil? So disgusting! Suddenly mushrooms sound a whole lot better!
And this bear is going to invent a modern way to fix them! I'll make the forest dance to a brand new drum!
Ugh!
Ha-ha!
With his mighty hammer, the brown bear can change the world!
Hey Bucky, I could use your help! I got all the mushrooms ready to hang up to dry them out for winter!
Mushrooms, mushroom! I'm on a roll here!
Huh?
Check out my amazing invention!
Uh, it's a barrel with warts?
Don't you see? Now every mushroom will be ours!
Thanks to my remarkable machine, the Rushzoomer Mushroomer 500!
So, it's not a wart barrel? How is it supposed to gather mushrooms, Bucky?
Prepare to witness the amazing!
One humble brown bear is about to show the whole entire world the way a master stalks up for the winter!
Ha-ha! Ha-ha! Ha-ha! Ha-ha! Ha-ha!
Yeah! Bjornie, look! Woo-hoo! Yeah! I love it!
I'm a rushzoomin' my tail off! Bucky the Bear is a genius! Ha-ha-ha! Ha-ha-ha!
Oh-oh-oh! Ha-he-ha-ha!
Yeah! Rushzoom! Gotcha! Gotcha-toot! Gotcha-toot! Ha-ha!
Ha-ha! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Well then, do you love it or do you love it? Greatest invention in bear history!
But Bucky, there's a lot of stuff, just not the right stuff.
Just look! Try! Dig around, you'll find mushrooms in there!
Well, I found some really nice leaves!
The wonderful bounty of the forest! Looks great!
Mmm!
Bleh! That tastes truly awful!
What if we mixed it with that yummy fish oil you were talking about?
Wait, that's the worst idea ever.
The polar bear is getting...
A pretty cool idea! Bucky, listen!
I already know it. The rushzoomer is nothing but a wart barrel.
My big important machine for picking mushrooms is a failure.
Bucky, it was not a failure.
While it may not be the best machine for collecting mushrooms,
it is super good at cleaning old leaves up.
I'm a genius! Ha-ha!
Just look at the...
D-leafinator 5000!
But I can make it even better!
Maybe...
What it needs is a motor!
Just a zillion or so horsepower and...
I could hook you up with some reindeer.
Forget reindeer and horses!
We can use genuine bear power!
Ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Bucky is up!
Bucky and Bjorn are both geniuses!
Best bear buddies, they've got the goods!
With their wonderful wagon cleaning up the woods!
Singing songs and cracking jokes!
We'll see you next time!
Cause that's all, folks!
B-b-b-b-bears!
Uh, did you put brakes on this thing?