Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
The weather forecast!
Bucky's limber, Bucky's spry
This bear is on fire!
Now let the badminton tournament begin!
I'm ready to win big!
Oh yeah? Well I'm ready to win bigger!
Game on guys!
Flam!
Hiya!
Shuttled cock retrieval!
Kaprow!
What are you, on break?
Stop the game! It's all over!
It's a tie!
I wanna win!
We have to keep going!
Let's do it then!
Bucky's pumped!
Bucky's spry!
This bear is...
Wet?
Run!
Save yourselves!
Hurry!
You ever see a wet bear?
We look ridiculous!
Oh, my fur is gonna be frizzy for a week!
Dumb old thunderstorm!
It spoiled our fun afternoon!
If only we'd known in advance that all this rain was coming!
Then we could've planned the tournament for a different time instead!
Hey, we could do that!
There's a way to predict future weather!
Let's go outside and I'll show you!
Well, we're outside!
Show us how to predict the weather!
We need to observe the birds!
If they're flying close to the ground, rain might be coming!
And if they're flying way up high, we're in for sunny weather!
But where are the birds?
There are none around!
Then we just have to wait!
Uh, idea!
No more waiting around!
Birds are for the birds!
What I'm gonna do is build a mechanical weather predictor!
Franny, Chickie, let's get going!
Yes!
See the saw!
See the saw-saw!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Aw, that is looking sweet!
Ahem, ahem!
Presenting my new awesome invention!
The truly brilliant, Raynomadic, Braynomadic!
Ta-da!
It's all very simple!
I put my avian macro chip right in the basket,
which the balloon then skyifies!
At the first sign of rain, the avian macro chip
relays a signal to those on the ground!
And that's that!
Any questions?
Good!
Where's my macro chip?
Ah!
Excellent!
If you see any weather, just be sure to let us know down here!
Good macro chip!
Woo-hoo!
Finally, there's a bird!
Flying high!
All right, that means rain's not coming!
I need to go tell the guys!
Yay!
Ah!
Chicky chip!
You're back!
And you're all wet!
Which must mean rain!
Ugh!
Oh!
Come and you're in!
Let's go!
No everything!
Anyway, how was the pilot so much fun?
No!
Oh!
heating on me?
No!
Honey!
Exactly!
No!
Oh!
That'd be fun!
Speaking!
Are you ready for blasting or warming?
Yeah!
Well, yeah!
All the PABYNERS read the banditos!
That I'm ready for thepark!
Myシ57-кеeta and I seem to believe here!
Very glyph!
Good to know what I was about to worry about!
which means that we won't be playing any more games.
Sigh.
I guess I should have built a snow-o-matic,
oh, heck, no-o-matic.
So, Bjorn, have you got some skis by any chance?
Of course! Skis, yeah!
We can have a tournament of winter badminton.
Uh-huh. This was a really cool idea.
Game on, guys!
Here comes my super serve!
Ha-blam-o!
Boom!
Krathwack!
Ha!
Ugh!
Yay!
Kapow!
Ha!
Ugh!
Shuttlecock retrieval!
Hey, is that a rain cloud?