If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together.
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky.
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky.
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Global Warming
Wait, wait, don't go!
It's too darn hot!
Now I know what a potato feels like when it's baking.
What a heat wave we're going through.
Phew, boy!
What a scorcher!
Wish I could take my fur off.
Hmm.
Genius time!
Must beat the heat!
Huh?
Poor little overheated beak face!
Chicky!
Don't worry!
I'll cool you down, pal!
Wait there!
Here!
And here!
Also here!
Also also here!
And here!
And here too!
Now, which wire leads to what?
Was it red or blue?
Or was it gray or gray?
I better unplug them both.
Just to be certain.
They're alive!
Alive!
You are so lucky to have a friend as smart as me.
You'll be cool in no time.
I just need to get some nice refreshing drinks from the fridge now.
Come to me, my lemonade!
Whoa!
No way!
It's even too hot inside the fridge!
This isn't just a heat wave.
This heat must be the work of global warming!
Well, all right then.
It's time to invent something that protects us from Mr. Sun!
This is my best idea ever!
Beat the heat!
Yeah!
Hi, Bucky!
I brought you some nice cold fruit punch!
Franny, thanks!
But I don't have time for punch!
I'm doing something really important!
Can you not see that I'm working hard on a machine that will block out the sun?
Great!
Why would you need to block out the sun?
To save the world from the terrors of global warming!
Look, Franny!
Just need a few props!
And there!
Say you're relaxing in the sun, just catching some rays,
and you start to get a little extra hot.
You start up your sweet sunblockinator-o-matic-tron and...
Shade!
Even on the hottest of days!
Huh?
A fire?
Looks like it's near Bucky's place!
I'm coming to rescue you, buddy!
Oh, Bjorn!
Hi there!
Want some fruit punch?
Hey there!
Bucky?
So, what's burning?
Nothing's burning!
It's worse!
Global warming is ravaging our planet!
Bjorn, my poor fridge is no longer cold!
It got warmed!
This is bad!
Hurry, we've gotta save our forest!
So, will you two boys have some of my punch or not?
Who cares about the punch?
Don't you die on us, forest!
Hey, come on!
Pump it, guys!
Keep on pumping it!
That's great!
You picked the wrong globe to warm, buster!
Put your back into it!
So, hero-esque!
Well, guess I should put the punch in the fridge!
Who cares about the punch?
The stuff is delicious!
That's weird.
It's been turned off.
Odd choice on such a hot day.
Oh, the pluggy's outie!
There you go, sweetie!
Now it'll cool right down!
See you later, Punchy!
Pump, you pumpers!
Pump like the wind!
Yes!
Take that, global warming!
Fellas, I'm heading home.
Bucky, I plugged your fridge back in for you and left some punch.
K, bye!
Uh, huh?
It wasn't global warming that did it then?
All this time, I unplugged the refrigerator myself?
And we both thought that we were saving the entire forest!
Pump, guys!
Pump like the wind!
That's Franny the Fox one, global warming zero!
Want some fruit punch?
That sounds amazing!
It's really hot out today!
Well, that's global warming for ya!