Taking walks and playing games when there's sunny weather
If there's rain, they're singing songs or reading books together
Every day just has a way of feeling extra lucky
When you spend it with a friend, just like Bjorn and Bucky
Just like Bjorn and Bucky!
Old-fashioned food!
The master chef at work!
His ancient secret recipe
Is a nutritious road map to yummy town!
Oh, here already?
Bwong, bwong, bwong, bwong!
Hi there! Come on in!
Hey!
Yummy!
Am I early Bjorn?
Not at all Buck!
It's almost ready!
What did you make?
Well?
Pie?
Well, it isn't pie, no!
Then what?
Cake?
Not cake, no sir!
Wait and see!
Is it cupcakes then?
It's not cupcakes!
It's ice cream!
Wrong again!
Well then what?
Are we even really going to have something?
Behold!
Smells so good, right?
This is our ancient northern recipe!
What's this stuff?
Soup?
Yeah!
Wise bears teach us to eat lots of food that's nutritious before the start of winter!
And this soup has lots of yummy things!
Mushrooms, cabbage, and carrots!
Just stop!
You said this wouldn't be some old dull lunch!
You promised a feast!
This is a feast where I'm from!
We call it Grand Poobot Chowder!
I opened a can of really special spongy mushrooms for it!
Thanks a lot Bjorn!
But soup doesn't sound that good to me!
I'd rather just stick with my yummy chips here!
I'm not that hungry!
If you're not really hungry, why do you keep eating all those chips then?
They're bad for you!
Remember, when summer's over, there won't be anything like this soup!
I sleep all winter long, so summer's never over for me!
And then I'm hungry!
I'm hungry!
And no cooking required!
But the way we did it, back up north…
Up north we did this and we did that!
Your ways are so old fashioned up north with your fungus weed soup or whatever!
But this is modern food!
It was made in a factory with machines and smart technology!
Well, if you don't like the kind of food that I make, then the next time you can cook!
Come on Bjorn!
Don't be upset!
Hey!
Listen!
I'll make something that's delicious for you!
So good your taste buds will explode!
Genius time!
I'll invent a recipe that's totally new!
It'll be… foodtastic!
Behold!
Nah, not good enough yet!
What else could I use?
Ha!
Gotta use gummy bears!
Nice!
Look so yummy!
Oh!
I love hot dogs too!
Ooh!
And meringue!
Chocolate of course!
Burgers!
Wait!
Wiener burgers!
Gingerbread!
Cookies!
Yeah!
Now lots of mayonnaise on top!
Ice cream!
And cupcakes!
It's so beautiful!
Super McDuper!
Now that is what I call a real beast!
I better get Bjorn over here before the ice cream melts!
Ha ha!
Bjorn, you are going to flip!
Prepare yourself!
You are about to be truly amazed!
Oh, wow!
Cool sculpture, Bucky!
It isn't a sculpture at all!
It's a super McDuper dish that I invented!
It sure is taller than your regular food!
It had to be big enough to fit all the flavor!
Now then!
Borg a train to yummy town!
Eat that stuff?
You really serious?
Trust me, you're going to be begging for seconds, thirds, tenths!
Ew!
Disgusting!
What?
Disgusting?
Impossible!
Gross, right?
You don't look so good, Buck!
You all right over there?
I'm just fine!
I've never had yummier food!
It's really nutritious as well!
Bucky?
Junk food avalanche!
Bucky, run!
No!
My beautiful recipe!
Lost!
Gone forever!
The food-manity!
Why?
And I just realized I'm starving.
It's all right, Bucky.
We'll clean the whole mess up.
And when we're done, you can reconstruct your dish.
Your modern and high-tech, disgusting, horrible, awful dish.
Uh, Bjorn, know what?
Let's head to your house.
You've got some soup left over there, s-
Ah!
Try not to lick the paint off the bowl.
Yeah!
Grand Poobot chowder!
They should call it Bucky's Bottomless Belly Bisque.
That is literally your tenth helping.
Can I have elevenths?
Please?